var questionArray = [
		{
			question: "As determined by the American Kennel Club, what is the most popular dog breed?", 
			answers: ["Golden Retreiver", "Labrador", "German Shepherd", "Border Collie", "Chihuahua"],
			correctAnswer: "Labrador"
			
		},	
		{
			question: "How many US Presidents have had dogs in the White House?", 
			answers: ["32", "27", "16", "39", "45"],
			correctAnswer: "27"
			
		},	
		{
			question: "About how many dogs are in the world?", 
			answers: ["400 million", "250 million", "600 million", "750 million"],
			correctAnswer: "400 million"
			
		},	
		{
		
			question: "What animal can dogs be traced back to?", 
			answers: ["Miacis", "Barbaturex", "Lorises", "Chiropetra", "Bonobo"],
			correctAnswer: "Miacis"
			
		},	
		{
		
			question: "Human have unique fingerprints, what is a dog's unique identifier?", 
			answers: ["Paw print", "Bark", "Nose print", "Tongue print", "Bite map"],
			correctAnswer: "Nose print"
			
		},	
		{
		
			question: "How many eyelids do dogs have?", 
			answers: ["Four", "Three", "Two", "One"],
			correctAnswer: "Three"
			
		},	
		{
		
			question: "Who owned the most dogs in history?", 
			answers: ["Kublai Kahn", "King of Norway", "Salvador Dali", "Pope Leo X", "Josephine Bonaparte"],
			correctAnswer: "Kublai Kahn"
			
		},	
		{
		
			question: "Which breed of dog is completely white at birth?", 
			answers: ["Airedale Terrier", "Weimaraner", "Siberian Huskies", "Dalmations"],
			correctAnswer: "Dalmations"
			
		},	
		{
		
			question: "What dog breed is known for its bluish-black tongue?", 
			answers: ["Akita", "Chow-Chow", "Akbash", "Ibzian Hound"],
			correctAnswer: "Dalmations"
			
		},	
		{
		
			question: "Which breed of dog changes as it ages both in how it looks and their coat texture?", 
			answers: ["Airedale Terrier", "Weimaraner", "Siberian Huskies", "Dalmations"],
			correctAnswer: "Airedale Terrier"
			
		},	
	];